<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 AndiCar - a car management software for Android powered devices.

 Copyright (C) 2010 Miklos Keresztes (miklos.keresztes@gmail.com)

 This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 (at your option) any later version.

 This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 GNU General Public License for more details.

 You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="ERR_000">"Database error."</string>
    <string name="ERR_001">"The start index is within an existing mileage"</string>
    <string name="ERR_002">"Stop/New index is within an existing mileage"</string>
    <string name="ERR_003">"New mileage overlap an existing mileage"</string>
    <string name="ERR_004">"Stop/New index must be greater than start index"</string>
    <string name="ERR_005">"Conversion rate already exist"</string>
    <string name="ERR_006">"Error on creating record!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_008">"Invalid date/time format!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_009">"This driver can not be deleted because it is used in mileage(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_010">"This driver can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_011">"This car can not be deleted because it is used in mileage(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_012">"This car can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_013">"This UOM can not be deleted because it is used in mileage(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_014">"This UOM can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_015">"This UOM can not be deleted because it is used in UOM conversion(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_016">"This currency can not be deleted because it is used in car definition(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_017">"This currency can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_018">"This expense type can not be deleted because it is used in mileage(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_019">"This expense type can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_020">"SDCARD not found. You can not create reports, gps tracks and database backups!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_021">"Report folder (/sdcard/andicar/reports) can not be created. You can not save the reports locally until you create this folder on your device."</string>
    <string name="ERR_022">"Can not create report file!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_023">"File writing error!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_024">"Backup folder (/sdcard/andicar/backup) can not be created. You can not backup your database until you create this folder on your device."</string>
    <string name="ERR_025">"The UOM can not be inactivated because it is used in an active car definition."</string>
    <string name="ERR_026">"The currency can not be inactivated because it is used in an active car definition."</string>
    <string name="ERR_027">"This category can not be deleted because it is used in refuel(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_028">"This category can not be deleted because it is used in expense(s)."</string>
    <string name="ERR_029">"The conversion rate is already defined between these currencies."</string>
    <string name="ERR_030">"This expense can not be deleted because it was created by a refuel.\nYou should delete the refuel."</string>
    <string name="ERR_031">"You can not define conversion between the same UOM's."</string>
    <string name="ERR_032">"You can not define conversion between the same currencies."</string>
    <string name="ERR_033">"GPS track folder (/sdcard/andicar/gpstrack) can not be created. You can not save the gps track files until you create this folder on your device."</string>
    <string name="ERR_034">"File system error!\nCheck your SDCARD."</string>
    <string name="ERR_035">"Invalid report."</string>
    <string name="ERR_036">"Track file not found!"</string>
    <string name="ERR_037">"Unknow car!\nIf this error persist, please report it at https://code.google.com/p/andicar/issues/entry"</string>
</resources>